Yes, I'm a patriot, and you will rub the
да я патриот а вы потрете
city and Khmelnytsky from Ukraine, and
я из украины город и хмельницкий а вы
where
откуда
are you from, what city are you from
вы из какого города
?  like
пацаны вы если такие смелые . типа
talk to me face to face if you are
общайтесь со мной глаза в глаза если
afraid then the way the girl to talk
боитесь то путь девушка поговорить
instead of you left
вместо вас ушел
I ask people from russia how you feel
я спрашиваю людей из россии как вы
about the war in ukraine
относитесь к войне в украине
very positively and
очень позитивно и
instagram is bad it's a horror teaching
instagram это плохо это ужас обучающим
to render things and now i can
оказывать вещи а теперь я могу а
and why you have been turned off instagram because
за что вам отключили instagram потому
what
что
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
why that's why it
почему вот почему он
turns out because russia
получается из-за того что россия напала
attacked ukraine data imposed sanctions,
на украину данными ввели санкции в том
including before they closed there
числе и до позакрывали там
and what else what else was closed in russia what
а что еще что еще закрыли в россии чего
there is no brand there heard
нету там бренда слышал
will end
закончится
russian sneakers do not produce
российские кроссовки не производят
russian sneakers what  x don’t
российские кроссовки что x не
say girl say russian
высказать девушка скажи российские
sneakers this is
кроссовки это что
why it turns out that russian
почему так получается что российские
sneakers are garbage but for western
кроссовки фигня а вот за западные
good
хорошие
money why a
за чем
normal dialogue video if you don’t
нормальный диалог видео вы если не
know how to do without swearing and sit
умеете без матюков и что-то сидите
shut up listen to how the girls look like
помолчите послушайте как девушки виду
they are doing business normally if you want
делу они ведут нормально если вы хотите
try to talk too normal we
попробуйте поговорить тоже нормальный мы
'll talk why why this aggression
поговорим зачем зачем вот эта агрессия
here I set normal  ny question so why,
вот я задаю нормальный вопрос так почему
for example, do you want to wear western things at night and you
например западные вещи они ночь вы
don’t want Russian
хотите носить а российские не хотите
plush no worse for some reason they
плюша не хуже почему-то
went to pieces to buy
пошли на куски покупать
Ukraine there is we in the city there is also a
украине есть есть мы в городе тоже
big market in the base there are a lot of things
большой рынок в основе очень много вещей
to the western ones there are also and in the spring the
до западных также есть а весны
city of Khmelnitsky and
город хмельницкий а
before  the role didn’t reach you and
до вас дошла роль на не не дошла и
guys the conditions that it’s funny I’ll say the cities
ребята условия что смешно я скажу города
where the war was going on guys
на которыми за шла война такие ребята
like you they don’t laugh there love
как вы они там не смеются люби умирают
children die and little ones it’s not very funny
дети и маленькие это очень не смешно
you understand that that is war it’s not funny
понимаете то есть война это не смешно
it’s not a reason to laugh there  it turned
это не повод там по смеха разосланы
out, well, at least out of respect for
вышло-то ну хотя бы из уважения к
everyone who died, just don’t laugh
погибшим всем так просто не смейтесь
well,
хорошо
girls, seriously, calmly argue,
девушки серьезно спокойно аргументируем
you can talk, the boys also want to
можно поговорить пацаны тоже хотят
talk, but they’re shy, I was also
поговорить но стесняются я тоже был
small, too, I remember yes,
мелким тоже помню да стеснялись мы
we were shy actually
вообще-то можем под матюки валили
if the guys
сильную да но давайте бром если ребята
want to ask something, ask me like
хотите что-то спросить спросите меня вот
this, I will also answer you without swearing
так же я вам тоже отвечу без матюков
ask here let the boys ask something
спросить вот пусть пацаны что-то спросят
ask there is a show  here you
спросить вот есть смотрите вот у вас
have the opportunity to ask something Ukrainians
есть возможность украинцы что-то
I will answer
спросить я отвечу
a lot of good people yes they have
хороших очень много людей да у них
someone who suffered in the war they languished at home and
кто-то пострадал на войне томили дома и
tass they don’t want they hate Russians
тасс они не хотят они ненавидят русских
if for example we came bombed
если бы например мы пришли бомбили
surgut so for example you would be fine too
сургут так например вы бы тоже хорошо вы
they would sit smiling at us, they would carve out bastards for
сидели улыбались бы нам выкроили [__]
you,
вам так
so your parents support the war
вот ваши родители поддерживают войну
at least for him,
хотя бы его
but as in one system, people who
а как в одной систем людям которые
are linked fled to Russia due to the fact that
сцеплены убежали в россию из-за того что
the shift began, you must see, yes, I
началась смена обязан смотрите да я
think that refugees where where to look and
считаю что беженцы куда куда смотреть и
refugees where they could go and
беженцы куда могли туда и убегали
for example, they fled from Mariupol, part of them fled on the
например из мариуполя часть убегала на
territory of Ukraine, part of them on the territory of
территории украины часть на территорию
Russia, who could lick where they were
россии кто куда мог кому куда был
and ran away like that, that is, to condemn
оближете и убегали так то есть осуждать
the fact that they fled there or there
того что они убегали туда или туда
at all, people ran away from
вообще не так люди убегали от боевых
hostilities,
действий
it is necessary to condemn those who started these
осуждать надо тех кто начал эти боевые
hostilities, then  there is russia attacked
действия то есть россия напала на
ukraine and it is the fault that
украину так и это есть вина в том что
people became refugees that is the question
люди стали беженцами вот в чем вопрос
there are more questions you can ask
есть еще вопросы можете спросить
you can use your words  ovami to formulate, I will
можете своими словами сформулировать я
understand or I can understand how
пойму или по могу понять как
to voice this question, and I
нибудь вот озвучить и этот вопрос а я
will try to help you with it in a
попробую помочь вам с ним
very negative way, because this is a man
очень негативно потому что это человек
who attacked my country, but how can
который напал на мою страну да как я
I treat him okay
могу к нему относиться ладно
well, because we have him, look
хорошо потому что он у нас смотрите у
here  where Lensky has his own questions, like
нас где ленскому есть свои вопросы как
powder, so we have not only that
порошенку были так у нас не только что
we love the president there, but now there
мы там любим президента просто но сейчас
is a war, he is fighting the president of a warring
идет война он воюет президент воюющей
country against the aggressor dossier yes, we will
страны против агрессора досье да мы его
support him in this when Ukraine
поддержим в этом когда то что украина по
hits its own no, look this is Russia
своим бьет нет это смотрите это россия
very  is doing some kind of propaganda so
очень делает кую пропаганду так вот
now also that Ukraine toastmaster why
сейчас также что украина тамада зачем
Ukraine hit its
украине бить по своей
Donbass this Ukraine was before Ukraine on the
донбасс это украина была до украина по
news you
новостям вы
see why they said so because
смотрите почему так говорили потому что
in the Donbass no one bombed anyone at all
на донбассе никто вообще никого не
there were no hostilities
бомбил не было никаких боевых действий
before April 12, 2014
до того как 12 апреля 2014 года
Russian  militants Girkin still a
российские боевики гиркин еще компания
company with grenade launchers with machine guns left the
так с гранатометами с автоматами вали с
territory of Russia to the Donetsk region and
территории россии в донецкую область и в
captured the city of Slavyansk  and the
городе славянск захватили отделение
police department of the SBU started where they put them in the basement
полиции сбу начали там где на подвал
, they shoot, and from that
сажать расстреливает так и с того
time hostilities began in the
времени начались боевые действия на
Donbas before that, no one
донбассе до этого не было никто не
died, look if, for example, I take
погибал смотрите если я например возьму
50 people in Surgut, I capture
50 человеке в сургуте захвачу
the police station, so I start killing
отделение полиции так начну убивать
people, militants will start coming
людей начнут приезжать боевики кит
from there we  we will be terrorists
оттуда мы будем террористами
earlier, yes, absolutely also
ранее да вот абсолютно также на
these terrorist groups began to enter the territory of Russia, this
территории россии начали заходить эти
is how they began to
террористические группы вот так начали
fire at Ukrainian positions, of course
обстреливать украинские позиции конечно
, the war began
началась война
until Russia, Russian
до того момента как россия российские
militants did not enter the territory of the length,
боевики не вошли на территорию длины
no one fought with anyone, they
никто ни с кем не воевал
told us and
рассказывали у нас и
I’ll say that I don’t remember  it
скажу не помню это
just started from what to ours from
только-только началось с чего на наш с
what event,
какого события
let’s say
допустим
some part of ukraine, I can’t
какая то часть украины то не могу
say it belonged to russia at first, but
сказать принадлежала сначала россия но
then somehow it
каким-то образом оно
became a
стало
nauseating conquest there, as it used to be
тошно завоеванием там как раньше было
, but in an honest way,
принято а вот и честным способом
you can say
скажешь
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
further in  don’t look as a gift, here
далее в качестве подарка не смотрите вот
I am, born 81 so ussr ra  I slept in the
я 81 года рождения так ссср распался в
ninety-first year at the time of the collapse of the
девяносто первом году на момент распада
USSR, Crimea was part of Ukraine, so I
ссср крым был частью украины вот я
was born in 880, 10 years before the collapse of the USSR,
родился в 880 за 10 лет до распада ссср
Crimea was already part of Ukraine and what a
крым уже был частью украины и каков
gift there was, that there
подарка там не было это что есть
was an
девяносто первом году появилась
independent state of Ukraine in the ninety-first year, an
независимое государство украина
independent state of the Russian
независимое государство российская
Federation yet  who recognized
федерация еще которые признавали границы
each other's borders in Russia in Ukraine in 97,
друг друга в россии в украиной в 97 году
even an agreement on friendship and cooperation was concluded,
даже был заключен договор о дружбе и
which clearly
сотрудничестве в котором четко было
stated that the countries recognize the borders and 1
сказано что страны признают границ и 1
each other Novak so there were no complaints
друг друга новак так никаких претензий
, and now when your
не было а теперь когда вот он вашему
leadership wanted to capture Crimea there
руководству захотелось захвате там крым
donets they tell you in schools like what
донец вам рассказывают в школах типа как
do you think the teacher who from
вы считаете учительница которые от
told she sincerely
рассказывала она искренне это
told it or she was simply forced from the
рассказывала или ее просто заставили из
department of education by the whole class
управление образования всем классом
to conduct such a lesson
провести такой урок
at the teacher’s school
школе учителя
I the teacher
я учительница
said you can say
сказала можете сказать
you say and that with
говоришь и что весом с
sincerity it’s good, look
искренностью хорошо вот смотрите
for example
например
we’ll take it like this  were there everything was
мы возьмем вот так были были там все
fine  yes, then the territory, even if
нормально когда то территории даже если
they donated something there, so we became
там что-то дарили так вот мы стали
independent states and already
независимыми государствами и уже жили
lived within such borders,
вот в таких границах
for example, you don’t come there from Japan
например не приходишь там от вас японии
or Germany to take something away from you because
или германии что-то отобрать потому что
only the date was Japanese or German is
только дата была японской или германском
true and
правда и
if you  what question am I asking
сама если вы вот какой вопрос я задаю
that’s all, for example, you are in Surgut,
вот все вот например вам в сургуте так
so you live far away in Surgut, that it
вот вы живете далеко в сургуте что вам
’s better for you that Russia took
лучше стало то что россия забрала
Ukraine to Crimea,
украины крым
but the territory is here for the boys, but
но территория вот пацанам а вот ведь
look at the territories when you are 18
территории смотри когда тебе станет 18
you will be taken into the Russian army and
тебя заберут в армию российскую так и
thrown where  -something to die for some
кинуть куда-то умирать за какую-то
territory conquered it you need and what
территорию завоевали она тебе нужно да о
you dreamed of
чем мечтал
going and want to go to a foreign country
поехать и хочешь ехать чужую страну
seizes a foreign country of some sort
захватывает чужую страну какой-то так
in which you dreamed of watching you live in
в чем вот мечтал о смотреть ты живешь в
Surgut so you can develop become a
сургуте так ты можешь развиваться стать
scientist become a businessman statins are
ученым стать бизнесменом статинами
just good  some kind of
просто хорошим человеком каким-то
worker, such a good father there, a friend, and
рабочим так хорошим отцом там другом и
so on, so the athletes
так дальше так спортсменам прославлять
glorify their Russia, for example, like this, but you want
свою россию например так у но ты хочешь
after 18 Tue at h  im to the military to
после 18 вт at him to военным чтобы
seize a foreign country so it’s just a dream
захватывать чужую страну так лишь мечта
it’s funny yes it’s funny while you are there in
это смешно да это смешно пока ты там в
Surgut and while you are small and then it’s not
сургуте и пока маленький а потом не
funny or war is scary for everyone
смешно или война это страшно для всех
absolutely for everyone
абсолютно для всех
but look
а вот смотри
here’s how you think Surgut lives
вот как вы считаете сургут багато живёт
richly lives
богато живет
probably and
наверное и
in the north, it’s hamlo from yugra, it’s probably the
севера то из югры хамло то наверное
top 3 most normal, but look
топ-3 самых нормально но смотрите
in good data, this khmao-yugra
в good data этот хмао-югра так
is oil workers, that is, in fact, you
это нефтяники то есть по сути у вас
produce oil
добывают нефть
oil gas, of course,
нефть газ это конечно
look, in fact, you have huge
посмотрите по сути у вас огромные
resources, so you live worse than
ресурсы так на живете вы хуже чем
for example  moscow or peter really
например москва или питер правда
8 you dare look like that, that is moscow
8 смеешь такое вот смотри то есть москва
so moscow-peter so they live better at the
так москва-питер так они живут лучше за
expense of your resources live better but you
счет ваших ресурсов живут лучше но вы
laugh that you have some
смеетесь что вам где-то крым какой-то
share of the crimea and why moscow and peter live better
доли а почему москва и питер живут лучше
than surgut
чем сургут сметки
these estimates  the kids who are watching,
эти детки которые смотрят
they examined it, just try
они рассмотрели вот просто попробуйте
to answer a simple question for me so if
мне ответить на простой вопрос так если
oil is produced from you huge resources and
нефть добывают у вас огромные ресурсы и
if oil is produced from you where is
если нефть добывает у вас где сургут
surgut why does peter-moscow live cool  than you
почему питер-москва живет круче чем вы
who extract oil there is more
которые добывают нефть там больше
population and people
населения и люди
make money how from what they make
делают деньги как из чего они делают
money because there are a lot of them and from what they
деньги потому что их много а с чего они
make money
делают деньги у
you have a lot of oil and few people that is, this
вас много нефти и мало людей то есть это
oil could provide a lot of
нефтью можно было обеспечить очень много
wealth so but for some reason  then this money is
богатство так но почему-то деньги эти
taken and the Moscow people are given it
забираются и московским людям даются
turns out to be in that infrastructure in those
получается в ту инфраструктуру в тех
people deposits from this they are you why are you
людей вклады из это они вас почему вы-то
deep on
пучин на
Zelenskaya
зеленская
heard in this on Zelensky
услышан в этом на зеленского
no they are normal just look like a face
нет они нормальные просто похоже лицом
many are ready to Zelensky it doesn’t look like good
многие готовы зеленским не похож доброго
evening
вечера
this girl didn’t humiliate me  and
меня не унижал эта девушка а
here come on guys who are you
вот вот сюда давайте пацаны которые вы
there rejoicing that the Crimea has come
там радуется что крым пришел
what is your name me
как тебя зовут меня андрей
andrey matveev stew matvey for me andrey
матвеев тушенка матвей для меня андрей
here look matvey did you live better
вот смотри матвей стал ли ты лучше жить
after russia took away the
после того как россия отобрала крыма
crimea ukraine and how is it better than
украина а как чем то лучше чем
what you started to live better  surgut for example
чем ты лучше стал жить сургуте например
[music]
[музыка]
tagil nizhny tagil even this one to share and
тагил нижний тагил даже вот эта делить и
began to live better after the annexation of the crimea
стал жить лучше после аннексии крыма
in which you just rejoice something we
в чем просто ты радуешься что-то мы
captured h
захватили чужую территорию
why,
почему раз
why is this the reason for your joy,
почему такая причина твоей радости
for example, when the Russian
например например когда российские
military steals into the washing machine, he has joy
военные ворует в стиралку у него радость
, she didn’t have a washing machine, now there is
уж у нее не было стиралки теперь есть
alcohol  that is,
школе рим так досочка вы это то есть там
tell me why are you there at all, this
кажи зачем ты там вообще есть это
parents are rather important, because did i
родители дуже важливо потому что did i
did it a bouquet of roses is it so you can’t
did it собой букет роз ли так не можно
hear and say fires of children so the
слышат и скажем пожаров детей так
results of ink from these then in
результатами тушь от этих то через
ten rocky was matvey ta ti logic you
десять рокки был матвей та ти логике вы
growth and will  a century of meat to go to ukraine,
роста и буду век мясу ехать в украину
in contrast, bite only ukraine,
такой в отличие выкуси лишь украину
because
потому
with children, the grass of other things, you are a cistern, we
с детьми трава прочего ты цистерна мы
go there and why don’t my grass be scared
туда и чем так траву мой будь не пугали
with our children, the injury of 500 excess
с нашими детьми травму 500 излишними
children of this cultivator, we account for their account,
детьми этого культиватор мы счет их счет
you will name for sufi details as in
ты назваешь за суфийских детали как на
winged politics  stan bums notre
крылатом политики стан бомжи нотр
turned out to be so and edit and
оказывалось так и edit а
both prices my kind and well there wants
обе цены мой вид и хорошо там хочет
rubles of olympus timber flock and hundreds of
рубли олимпа timber стая и сотнями
pacinos i appeared so and queen  rice, well,
пачино я проявлялись так и queen рис ну
it’s the same and here you both already drooped
так самая и тут вот вы уже оба чем отвис
molded org can pedro steven harm
формованный орг могут педро стивен вреда
there, after all, their paws break out of
там все-таки лапы их это вырваться из
shorter where to go and something there to
короче куда чтобы поехать и что-то там
curl someone else’s soul scourge especially cool and
завивать чужую душу бичуют особо круты а
who really wants, that is, thoughts there
кто сильно хочет то есть мысли там
besiege adequately and then, well, it’s
besiege адекватно и тогда ну дуже
really respectful ukraine and the bride’s
важливо украина п в невесты
propaganda is correct and sir from the Russian
пропаганду правильно и сэр от российскую
hammer of Russian orphans so far
молот российских детей-сирот сих пор
shuffling into the Russian nasals with the help
шарки в российскую носовыми помощью мы
of  from iran,
ты с рядом заменил от из ирана по
essentially, it needs a zmin j robot of
существу трэба змин j робот
denazification of
денацификации
adequate discord and inadequate
адекватных разлад и неадекватных первых
first, it’s so through the massacres materials so
у это так через резни материалы так
through the massacres from conversations such through the massacres
через резни от беседы такие через резни
there, and then through the cartoons he hears
там виду а то через мультики he hears
the cut me but from the composition kept
the cut me but из состава держал на
our position again
позиция наша повторно
rusich kumola you  soul and soul important for a
русич кумола ты души и душа важную для
shotgun answered and use write
дробовика ответила и пользуйтесь пишите
comments put likes it is important
коментарии ставте лайки це дуже важливо
and subscribe to the thaler channel
и подписывайтесь на талером канал
sent moxie glory to
послали moxie слава украине
ukraine  us even bootur here and
у нас даже боотур вот и